Finding Aid to the AIDS History Project — Ephemera Collection, 1973, 1981-2002 MSS.2000.31
University of California, San Francisco Archives & Special Collections
- Posters and Oversized Items, 1981-2002; Series 2; Box 4 and Map Case: 69 items
  - Large Oversize Posters and Ephemera
    - San Francisco/San Francisco Aids Foundation Oversize (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - "Fighting For Our Lives/AIDS Candlelight March," B/w poster mounted on foam core, San Francisco AIDS Foundation, [18-1/4" x 25-1/2"], ca. Monday May 2, 1983. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 20)
      - "We Know Someone Who Would Love Your Infamous Tuna Casserole," Shanti Project, [28" x 11"] Photo: Denise Joy. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 21)
      - "Brothers: Concerned about HIV & AIDS?" The Brother's Network. b/w poster, [17" x 22"] (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 22)
      - AIDS. All Individuals Deserve Support." AIDS Awareness week, SF Community College district, San Francisco AIDS Francisco. Art by TP. Ranger., ca. April 7 – 11, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 23)
      - "Women can get AIDS. You can take care of yourself." December 1. World AIDS Day. San Francisco General Hospital, San Francisco Women's AIDS Network. (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 24)
      - "EACH: Early Advocacy & Care for HIV: It's about Men of Color." Department of Public Health City & County of San Francisco, Design by John Tomlinson. Photo: Ira Nowinski. [18" x 23"] (Box 7, Folder 9, Item 25)